Contact

0867618606 (Mobile) hoskenchristopher@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/christopherhosken (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Programming
Team Management
Film Production

Languages

French (Limited Working)
English (Native or Bilingual)

Christopher Hosken

VFX & Technical Artist

Chiang Mai, Thailand

Summary

Hi! I'm Chris, a 17-year-old Technical Artist aspiring to be part of the film industry. I love working in teams and others have described me as a natural team leader. I also love a good challenge and always push to do the best that I can.

Experience

BOAP Studios

2 years 2 months

Director

September 2020 - April 2021 (8 months)

During my second year at BOAP Studios, I took on the role of director for the short film, Proxima. Alongside co-writing and envisioning the story, I also worked with the R&D team to develop our own facial motion capture plugin. As well as that, I helped with modeling and animation.

Producer

March 2019 - September 2020 (1 year 7 months)

During my first year and a half at BOAP Studios, I helped with writing, modeling, and animation alongside managing a small team of artists. I learned the foundations of how a studio operates, and what to do when conflicts arise amongst the team.

Education

Chiang Mai International School
High School Diploma, High School/Secondary Diplomas and
Certificates · (August 2010 - June 2023)